# Nameer Iqbal Ansari

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan



niansari@students.uit.edu



03363033155



linkedin.com/in/nameer-ansari-136944209

## Summary

This is NAMEER IQBAL ANSARI aka N.i.AnXari. Currently, Studying BE (Computer system engineering) at the USMAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY. Meanwhile, Working in MERL(Micro Electronic research lab) as a RESEARCH INTERN at UITU Karachi, a trainee at Xcelerium, and a GSoC'22 contributor, and the journey continues.

He is a dedicated, organized, and methodical individual. Have good interpersonal skills, an excellent team worker, and a keen and very willing to learn and develop new skills. He is reliable and often seeks new responsibilities within a wide range of challenging areas.

## **Experience**



## RTL Designer

**NOVA** 

Feb 2022 - Sep 2022 (8 months)

NOVA is an open-source RISCV-based Application Class SoC. its objective is to provide students with hands-on development experience with the latest technologies. and focus on the latest open-source tools and low-cost development methodologies. It has been verified in AWS FPGA prototypes.

#### MERL Research Intern

Micro Electronics Research Lab

Mar 2021 - Present (1 year 10 months)



#### Contributor

Google Summer of Code

Jun 2022 - Sep 2022 (4 months)

"Add FuseSoC support at SoC level for Azadi-SoC and Rebase ibex core with latest commit" is the project I've working on.

#### Education



#### Usman Institute of Technology

electrical engineering, Computer Technology/Computer Systems Technology 2019 - 2023



## Adamjee Government Science College

Intermediate, ENGINEERING 2017 - 2017



S.M.Public Academy

Matriculation, Computer Science 2006 - 2017

## **Skills**

YAML • Fusesoc • Cloud FPGA • Verilog • C++ • Xilinx Vivado • Linux • MATLAB • Proteus

## **Honors & Awards**



## Scholarship - HASHAM CHARITABLE FOUNDATION

Oct 2022

Got a scholarship in the 7th semester for one year on the bases of current CGPA.